Polymarket is now
raising $1 billion
in a $21 billion
valuation.
So now in September,
this prediction market
is worth 40% more than
it was in April.
So this round is led by
1789 Capital,
which is also the firm
that Donald Trump Jr.
is part of.
But they've invested
in a lot of things,
including SpaceX,
Substack, the Tucker
Carlson Network.
Pretty insane to
see here.
I remember when I worked
at a bank, they did not
like the prediction
market thing.
They called it gambling.
So it's pretty insane
to see this much
investment going
into it.
Polymarket was around
a $15 billion valuation
in April when D.E.
Shaw became an investor.
So they are
just slightly lagging
behind their main rival,
Kalshi, who raised
in May and are around
a $22 billion valuation.